Mr Hulton's waiting for you
in the yard, Mr Herriot.
Hulton 先生
在院子里等你，Herriot 先生。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Mrs Hall?
霍尔太太？
Look at this, Mrs Hall.
看看这个，霍尔夫人。
There's a hole in my
cricket flannels. So there is.
我的
板球法兰绒上有一个洞。所以有。
I can't wear them
on Sunday with a hole.
我不能
在星期天穿有洞的。
What would Mrs Pumphrey say?
Pumphrey 夫人会怎么说？
It's a good thing the Lord
invented darning then. Right.
那时上帝
发明了织补是一件好事。对。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I've just been speaking to
Richard Alderson. Oh, aye?
我刚刚和
理查德·奥尔德森谈过。哦，是吗？
Apparently, we're still a man
short for Sunday.
显然，我们仍然是一个
缺少星期天的人。
It's bad enough that we've
lost our top batsman.
我们
失去了顶级击球手，这已经够糟糕了。
Tristan, I know you're still unhappy
with me, but this - this is cricket.
特里斯坦，我知道你仍然对
我不满意，但这是 - 这是板球。
The annual Darrowby
match at Pumphrey Manor.
一年一度的 Darrowby
比赛在 Pumphrey Manor 举行。
You're not just punishing me,
you know,
你不只是在惩罚我，
你知道，
you're letting down the whole team.
Look, I told you -
你让整个团队都失望了。
看，我告诉过你——
I can't play for the Darrowby 11 any
more. Oh, that's just nonsense!
我不能再为 Darrowby 11 演奏了
。哦，那简直是胡说八道！
It's for local farmers
and vets by invitation.
它是由当地农民
和兽医邀请的。
And I, last time I checked,
am neither.
而我，上次检查时，
两者都不是。
Herriot.
赫里奥特。
Thanks so much for coming out.
No trouble at all.
非常感谢你出来。
一点都不麻烦。
I understand you've a bull needs
ringing? I do indeed. This way.
我知道你有一头公牛需要
敲响？我确实。这边走。
Here he is.
他在这里。
This is Monty.
这是蒙蒂。
Only a year old,
but he's a powerful fellow.
才一岁，
却是个厉害的家伙。
No, I can see that! We also need to
move him later today,
不，我看得出来！
今天晚些时候我们也需要移动他，
so if you could sedate him
once you've got the ring in.
所以如果你能在戴上
戒指后让他镇静下来。
That shouldn't be a problem.
那应该不是问题。
HE GRUMBLES
他抱怨
I will need a couple more men to
hold him, though.
不过，我还需要几个男人来
抱他。
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
他清了嗓子
So, Hugh definitely said
it was about a bull?
所以，休肯定说
这是关于公牛的？
That's what he said. He's got a new
bull that needs ringing.
他就是这么说的。他有一只
需要振铃的新公牛。
And he specifically asked for James?
他还特地问了詹姆斯？
He did.
他做到了。
It's about Helen.
It's got to be.
是关于海伦的。
它必须是。
I reckon James'
sins finally found him out.
我想詹姆斯的
罪孽终于找到了他。
Don't be daft.
别傻了。
James has done nothing wrong.
詹姆斯没有做错任何事。
Tell that to Hugh Hulton.
告诉休·赫尔顿。
I won't be a moment.
我不会是片刻。
Just going to give him an injection
of local anaesthetic.
刚打算给他打一针局
麻药。
Don't most vets just go ahead
and punch the hole?
大多数兽医不是直接
冲孔吗？
They do...
CALF GRUMBLES
他们确实......
小腿咕噜声
I find this way works better.
我发现这种方式效果更好。
HE GROWLS
他咆哮
All right, almost done...
好了，差不多完成了……
Easy now.
现在很容易。
FLESH PUNCTURES
肉刺
Huh, look at that.
Didn't bother him at all.
呵呵，看那个。
根本没有打扰他。
It usually works.
它通常有效。
Now, we just need the ring...
现在，我们只需要戒指...
So have I missed very much
while I've been away in France?
那么我
在法国旅行期间是否非常想念？
Er, no, not that I can think of.
No great Darrowby dramas to report?
呃，不，不是我能想到的。
没有伟大的达罗比戏剧要报道？
No, just things chugging along,
you know.
不，只是事情进展顺利，
你知道。
Have you seen much of Helen?
你见过很多海伦吗？
No, not a great deal.
不，不是很多。
But, well, now and again, you know.
但是，嗯，时不时地，你知道。
She seems well, does she?
她看起来很好，是吗？
Yes... Yes, far as I can tell.
是的……是的，据我所知。
Right, shall we get on with this,
then?
对了，那我们继续
吗？
I'm going up there later, actually,
to Heston Grange. Oh, yes?
我稍后会去那里，实际上，
去赫斯顿格兰奇。哦是的？
HE GROWLS
他咆哮
Whoa! Easy, Monty.
I say, James, are you all right?
哇！容易，蒙蒂。
我说，詹姆斯，你还好吗？
Come on ,Monty now.
Calm down.
来吧，蒙蒂。
冷静下来。
I think I'll live. Glad to hear it.
我想我会活下去。听到那个消息很开心。
THEY CHUCKLE
他们咯咯地笑
DOGS BARK, YAP
狗吠，做
So what's the verdict? Any hope?
Oh, there's always hope.
那么判决结果是什么？有希望吗？
哦，总是有希望的。
The adjustment nut's a bit stiff,
but once I've worked it loose,
调整螺母有点僵硬，
但一旦我松开它，
I can raise the bob
and she'll run right to time.
我可以举起鲍勃
，她会及时跑。
That's all it needs?
这就是它所需要的吗？
Well, you have to know how
far to raise it.
好吧，您必须知道
将其提高到什么程度。
Oh, of course. I don't doubt it
takes a lot of expertise.
哦，当然。我不怀疑这
需要很多专业知识。
Oh, don't know about that.
哦，不知道这个。
The main thing to remember is
lower is slower and left is lower.
要记住的主要事情是
较低的速度较慢，而左侧的较低。
Turn it to the right,
it'll go faster.
向右转，
它会跑得更快。
That's it.
就是这样。
Ah, so you've a cricketer
in the house. Hm?
啊，所以你
家里有一个板球运动员。嗯？
Oh, we've two.
哦，我们有两个。
But it's Mr Farnon Senior who's
playing in the match on Sunday.
但
参加周日比赛的是老法农先生。
To be honest, I've never
understood the appeal.
老实说，我从来没有
理解这种吸引力。
I know,
and I call myself a Yorkshireman!
我知道，
我称自己为约克郡人！
SHE CHUCKLES
她笑了
You'll be at the match, I take it?
I will.
你会参加比赛，我接受吗？
我会。
In fact, I'll be scoring.
事实上，我会得分。
Ah, so you're something
of an expert?
啊，所以你是
专家？
An amateur enthusiast, perhaps.
也许是业余爱好者。
Anyway, I'll...
反正我会...
I'll let you get on.
我让你上。
Oh, and thanks for the tea. Mm-hm.
哦，谢谢你的茶。嗯嗯。
What time did Hugh say he'd be up?
11 o'clock.
休说他几点起床？
11点钟。
And he just said it
where about the lease? He did.
他只是说
租约在哪里？他做到了。
So d'you think he wants to sell?
所以你认为他想卖吗？
Is that what he's coming to tell us?
You know as much as I do.
这是他来告诉我们的吗？
你知道的和我一样多。
What if he's decided
not to renew the lease
如果他决定
不续租怎么办
because of what happened between me
and him?
因为我
和他之间发生了什么？
Then I'd say you were right
not to marry him.
那么我会说你
不嫁给他是对的。
PHONE RINGS
电话铃声
Darrowby, 2-2-9-7.
达罗比，2-2-9-7。
I'm sorry, I can barely hear you.
对不起，我几乎听不到你的声音。
Ah, Mrs Pumphrey!
啊，普弗里夫人！
Hello, is everything all right?
你好，一切都好吗？
Mr Farnon?
法农先生？
No, I see.
不，我明白了。
Well of course, if it's a
matter of "great delicacy".
当然，如果
是“美味佳肴”的话。
I'll tell him now.
我现在就告诉他。
That was Mrs Pumphrey.
那是 Pumphrey 夫人。
She asked if you could go up
to the manor.
她问你是否可以去
庄园。
Doesn't she want Tricki's
Uncle Herriot? Apparently not.
她不是想要特里奇的赫里奥
叔叔吗？显然不是。
She said the matter requires
the utmost discretion.
她说这件事需要
最大的自由裁量权。
Intriguing. Mm-hm!
耐人寻味。嗯嗯！
"The utmost discretion"?
“最大的自由裁量权”？
What's all that about?
那是怎么回事？
I've no idea -
she said she'll only discuss it
我不知道 -
她说她只会讨论它
with Siegfried... In person.
与齐格弗里德...亲自。
Hm!
嗯！
So, spill the beans.
所以，洒豆子。
What happened at Hulton Hall?
休尔顿厅发生了什么？
Not a great deal.
不是很多。
What, Hugh didn't challenge you
to a duel for Helen's hand?
什么，休没有挑战你
为了海伦的手决斗？
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but, no.
很抱歉让你失望了，
但是，不。
Well, has he seen her yet?
嗯，他见过她吗？
Er, no, he said he was going up
later today.
呃，不，他说他
今天晚点上去。
And that doesn't bother you?
这不打扰你吗？
Of course not. Why should it?
当然不是。为什么要呢？
No reason.
没理由。
Where are you off to? Nowhere.
你要去哪里？无处。
I just, erm...
I need run an errand. Oh.
我只是，呃...
我需要跑腿。哦。
He's here!
他在这儿！
He's here.
他在这儿。
Hullo there. How do.
你好。怎么办。
You got back all right, then?
那你回来还好吗？
I did. Yes. Thank you.
我做到了。是的。谢谢你。
Can I make you a cup of tea? Er, no,
no, thanks. I can't stay long.
我可以给你泡杯茶吗？呃，不，
不，谢谢。我不能久留。
You said you wanted to speak to us
about the lease?
你说你想和我们
谈谈租约？
Yes, yes, that's right. Er...
是的，是的，没错。呃...
Ah, here we go.
啊，我们走了。
I intend to renew the lease
on the farm
我打算续签
农场的租约
for the agreed period of 20 years,
在约定的 20 年期间，
as per our existing contract,
根据我们现有的合同，
but with a couple of
additional stipulations.
但有一些
额外的规定。
The lawyers have added
Helen's and Jenny's names
律师加了
海伦和珍妮的名字
and specified that they'll inherit
the lease on the same terms.
并指定他们将以
相同的条款继承租约。
That's assuming that they want
to continue farming.
那是假设他们想
继续耕种。
That's wonderful. Thank you.
那好极了。谢谢你。
Thank you, Hugh.
谢谢你，休。
It's very good of you.
Not at all, it's...something
你真好。
一点也不，它是……东西
that should have been done years
ago, but erm...
那应该在几年
前完成的，但是呃...
Well, it didn't really seem
necessary before.
好吧，以前似乎没有
必要这样做。
Er...
Anyway, I think that
just about covers it.
无论如何，我认为这
几乎涵盖了它。
I don't want to take up too
much of your time,
我不想占用你太多
时间
but there's something I'd like
to show you, back at the farm.
但有件事我想
给你看，回到农场。
I don't understand. Consider it a
replacement, or apology,
我不明白。把它
当作替代品或道歉，
if you like, for the difficulties
with the sale of your last bull.
如果你愿意，因为
出售你最后一头公牛的困难。
Hugh,, this is too much...
We can't accept this.
休，这太过分了……
我们不能接受。
Please, Mr Alderson.
It would mean a great deal.
拜托了，奥尔德森先生。
这将意味着很多。
He's good breeding stock,
excellent condition...
他是优良种畜，
条件极佳...
Ah, well even so...
I would really like to make amends.
啊，即便如此……
我真的很想弥补。
Dad, why don't we think about it,
eh?
爸爸，我们为什么不考虑一下，
嗯？
That's all I ask.
这就是我要问的。
Just keep him here for now
and let me know what you decide.
现在
就让他留在这里，让我知道你的决定。
Right. All right, then. Excellent.
对。那好吧。优秀。
Right, better get on.
对，最好继续。
Hugh.
休。
Do you have to rush straight
off? Afraid so.
需要直接冲
吗？怕是这样。
Estate business has rather piled up
while I've been away.
我不在的时候，房地产生意就堆积如山。
No doubt see
you at the cricket on Sunday.
毫无疑问
，周日板球赛上见。
You will. Jolly good.
你会。欢乐的好。
Thank you so much for coming.
非常感谢你的到来。
Not at all, I understand
Tricki has been rather distressed?
完全没有，我知道
Tricki 一直很苦恼？
He's not himself at all.
他根本不是他自己。
Is he off his food?
Feeling lethargic?
他不吃东西了吗？
感觉昏昏欲睡？
Oh, no, no, there's no
problem in that department.
哦，不，不，
那个部门没有问题。
In fact, if anything, his appetite's
more robust than ever.
事实上，如果有的话，他的胃口
比以往任何时候都更加旺盛。
No, it's just, erm...
不，这只是，呃...
He's become...
他变成了...
..increasingly...
..日益...
..amorous towards things.
..对事物充满热情。
It's quite unsettling.
这很令人不安。
In the end,
I had to take his cushion away.
最后，
我不得不把他的垫子拿走。
HE SNEEZES
他打喷嚏
I see...
我懂了...
Well, let's have a look at him,
shall we?
好吧，让我们看看他，
好吗？
You know, Mrs Pumphrey,
the behaviour you're describing,
你知道，Pumphrey 夫人，
你所描述的行为，
is perfectly normal.
完全正常。
Tricki's a healthy animal
in the prime of life.
特里奇是一个
处于壮年期的健康动物。
And, as such, he's experiencing
some very natural...urges.
而且，因此，他正在经历
一些非常自然的......冲动。
Yes, but he's just a baby!
是的，但他只是个婴儿！
He's never shown the slightest bit
of interest in...
他
对……从来没有表现出丝毫的兴趣。
..that sort of thing.
..诸如此类的事情。
Well, it's a testament to the
excellent level of care
嗯，这证明了
出色的护理水平
he's been receiving. His weight's
gone down, his exercise has gone up.
他一直在接收。他的体重减轻
了，运动量增加了。
He's obviously feeling a great
deal livelier in every department.
显然，他
在每个部门都感觉更加活跃。
You know, Francois did say
that on one of their outings,
你知道，弗朗索瓦
在他们的一次郊游中确实说过，
he seemed intent on getting
into Mr Handshaw's yard.
他似乎
很想进入汉德肖先生的院子。
And does Mr Handshaw own
a dog at all?
Handshaw 先生到底
有没有养狗？
Oh, yes, a terrier.
哦，是的，一只小猎犬。
Named Bella, I believe.
我相信名叫贝拉。
Well, that would certainly explain
it.
嗯，这当然可以解释
它。
Less lethargic, more lothario.
不那么昏昏欲睡，更加乐于助人。
So what can be done
to discourage it?
那么可以做些什么
来阻止它呢？
I'm afraid the heart wants
what it wants,
恐怕心想要
什么，
which, in Tricki's case,
would seem to be Bella. Oh, dear.
在 Tricki 的情况下，
这似乎是 Bella。哦亲爱的。
There is one effective
course of action.
有一种有效
的行动方案。
It's a fairly simple procedure...
这是一个相当简单的程序...
Oh, no, no, no, no, Mr Farnon, no.
哦，不，不，不，不，法农先生，不。
Can't you just give him
a calming draught of some sort?
你就不能给他
一些平静的草稿吗？
I'm sorry, Mrs Pumphrey.
He'll have to be fixed.
对不起，庞弗里夫人。
他必须得到修复。
If not, Tricki will simply continue
his pursuit until he succeeds.
如果没有，特里奇只会继续
他的追求，直到他成功。
HE WHINES SOFTLY
他轻声呜咽
Hello, James.
Hello, Jenny. Hello, Scruff.
你好，詹姆斯。
你好，珍妮。你好，斯克鲁夫。
Wait till you see what
Hugh Hulton's brought us.
等你看看
休·赫尔顿给我们带来了什么。
Have you ever seen anything like it?
你见过类似的东西吗？
And he'll be worth
a fortune in stud fees.
而且他
在种马费上会值一大笔钱。
But Hugh won't accept a penny
for him, says it's an apology
但休不会
为他接受一分钱，说这是道歉
because he wants to move forward
with a clean slate.
因为他想
白手起家。
Jenny, run and put the kettle on.
珍妮，快跑，把水壶放上去。
Dad'll be wanting a brew
and I'm sure James'd like one.
爸爸会想要一杯啤酒
，我敢肯定詹姆斯会想要一杯。
Fine.
美好的。
A pedigree bull.
一头纯种公牛。
Quite the gift. I know.
相当的礼物。我知道。
It were the last thing we expected.
这是我们所期望的最后一件事。
We haven't said we'll take him yet.
我们还没有说要带走他。
Dad thinks it's far too much,
but even so...
爸爸认为这太过分了，
但即便如此......
And there you were, worried he might
not even renew the lease.
你在那里，担心他
甚至可能不会续签租约。
I know, that's all sorted now too.
我知道，现在这一切也都已经解决了。
He's even added mine and Jenny's
names, so it'll be ours to inherit.
他甚至还加上了我和珍妮的
名字，所以继承权是我们的。
Right. That's very decent of him.
对。这对他来说是非常体面的。
Now, then...
接着...
Mr Alderson.
奥尔德森先生。
What do you reckon?
你怎么看？
He's a fine specimen.
他是一个很好的标本。
He is that.
他就是那个。
Any luck with Reg Dutton, dad?
Nah, he's still over in Listondale.
爸爸，Reg Dutton 好运吗？
不，他还在利斯顿代尔。
Dad's a player down for match
on Sunday. Oh, yes?
爸爸是
周日参加比赛的球员。哦是的？
And with Hugh back, they'll be
really up against it.
随着休的回归，他们将
真正反对。
Hugh's on the opposing team?
He's captain.
休在对方球队？
他是船长。
Not to mention the star player. He's
the main reason they always win.
更不用说明星球员了。他是
他们总是获胜的主要原因。
Er, not always.
呃，并非总是如此。
Though Hugh is a good bowler,
there's no denying it.
尽管休是一名出色的投球手，
但不可否认。
You know, Mr Alderson,
你知道，奥尔德森先生，
if you need an extra man,
I'd be happy to help out.
如果你需要一个额外的人，
我很乐意帮忙。
I didn't know you played.
我不知道你玩过。
Yes, well, now and again... Oh, aye.
是的，嗯，时不时……哦，是的。
You reckon you're up to it,
do you, lad?
你认为你能
胜任，是吗，小伙子？
Absolutely.
绝对地。
Right.
对。
You're in.
你在。
I'm really not much of a cricketer,
我真的不是一个板球运动员，
but I guess
if it's just a friendly match,
但我想
如果这只是一场友谊赛
it's not too much to worry about.
不用太担心。
Friendly?
友好的？
James, I would not be exaggerating
to say that this is the most
詹姆斯，我不会夸张
地说这是最
important game in the
cricketing calendar.
板球日历上的重要比赛。
Once a year, the Darrowby 11
goes up against the might
一年一次，达罗比 11 逆势
而上
of Hulton Hall's invited gentlemen,
playing for the honour of Darrowby.
Hulton Hall 邀请的绅士们，
为 Darrowby 的荣誉而战。
And get annihilated.
That's hardly the point.
并被歼灭。
这不是重点。
It's really quite the event, James.
詹姆斯，这真的很重要。
Mrs Pumphrey holds it on her own
private ground.
Pumphrey 夫人在她自己的
私人土地上持有它。
Sorry, she has a cricket pitch?
抱歉，她有板球场？
Ground, yes, down beyond
the orchard.
地面，是的，
在果园外。
The old dear's
completely cricket-mad.
老亲爱的
完全板球疯狂。
So, when you say you're
"not much of a cricketer"...?
所以，当你说你
“不是一个板球运动员”时......？
Well, football's more my game.
嗯，足球更像是我的游戏。
But you have played?
Once or twice, probably just once.
但是你玩过吗？
一次或两次，可能只有一次。
Oh, dear.
哦亲爱的。
Well, I had no idea it was so
important.
好吧，我不知道它如此
重要。
Oh, I'd say it's important!
哦，我会说这很重要！
For a Yorkshireman,
it goes King, God, Cricket.
对于约克郡人来说，
它是国王，上帝，板球。
I mean, if you get this wrong,
我的意思是，如果你弄错了，
they'll string you up in the town
square. Oh, fiddlesticks!
他们会在城镇
广场把你绑起来。哦，小提琴手！
James is fast and he's fit.
All right, it's not his game,
詹姆斯速度很快，而且他很健康。
好吧，这不是他的游戏，
but with a bit of coaching,
he'll do perfectly well.
但
只要稍加指导，他就会做得很好。
Quite right. We'll soon whip you
into shape, lad.
非常正确。我们很快就会让你
恢复体型，小伙子。
So, we've a day and a half.
所以，我们有一天半的时间。
That's what, 14, 15 hours of
sunlight?
那是什么，14、15个小时的
阳光？
Now, when you played before,
现在，当你以前玩的时候，
would you say you were more of a
batsman or a bowler?
你会说你更像是
击球手还是投球手？
Well, neither really.
嗯，也不是。
It was on the beach at Troon and it
was probably more what
它在特伦的海滩上，
可能更重要
you would call French cricket.
COLLECTIVE INHALE
你会称之为法国板球。
集体吸气
But it can't be any tougher
than football.
但它不可能
比足球更难。
At least in cricket,
no-one tackles you.
至少在板球比赛中，
没有人会对付你。
You haven't had a cricket ball
coming at you at 80mph.
您还没有
以 80 英里/小时的速度向您扑来板球。
Seriously, James, one of those could
kill you.
说真的，詹姆斯，其中一个可能会
杀了你。
Right, follow me.
对了，跟我来。
Jess, come on, give that,
the boys need it for the cricket.
Jess，来吧，给那个，
男孩们需要它来打板球。
Thank you. Right, come on.
谢谢你。对了，来吧。
Right, James. Take your guard.
对，詹姆斯。做好防护。
Remember, middle and leg,
head over the ball, straight back.
记住，中间和腿，
头在球上，向后挺直。
Weight on the front foot...
前脚的重量...
And nice easy lob...
和漂亮的轻松吊球...
You need to maintain your guard.
你需要保持警惕。
How's he getting on? Try again...
他过得怎么样？再试一次...
You could give your brother a hand.
你可以帮助你的兄弟。
Yes, and he could apologise
for treating me like a fool.
是的，他可以
为把我当傻子而道歉。
But I don't see that happening any
time soon either. And...
但我也认为这种情况不会
很快发生。和...
James, please, try to concentrate!
I...!
詹姆斯，请尽量集中注意力！
一世...！
Right, once more, take your guard,
middle and leg...
对了，再一次保护好你的
中间和腿……
Oh, for the love of God.
James, pass it here.
哦，为了上帝的爱。
詹姆斯，把它传到这里。
Right, don't even think about
hitting it,
对了，别想着
打它，
just think about blocking it.
Blocking it?
只要考虑阻止它。
挡住了吗？
You just need to get behind the ball
and stop it, all right? Come on.
你只需要在球后面
停下来，好吗？来吧。
As long as it doesn't hit your leg
or the wicket, you'll stay in.
只要它没有碰到你的腿
或检票口，你就会留在里面。
Well, there's a little more to it,
than that...
嗯，还有更多的东西，除此之外
......
No, there isn't, not for James. But,
as ever, you're making everything
不，没有，不是为了詹姆斯。但是，
一如既往，你正在创造一切
10,000 times more complicated than
it has to be...
比
它必须的复杂10,000倍......
He needs to know what
he should be doing...
他需要知道
他应该做什么……
No, he needs you to stop confusing
him with pointless stuff.
不，他需要你停止
用毫无意义的东西迷惑他。
Just let the man breathe and he'll
work it out for himself.
只要让这个人喘口气，他就会
自己解决。
James. Here, give it a try.
詹姆士。来，试一试。
Right, that's it, just relax,
all you need to do is block it.
对，就是这样，放轻松，
你需要做的就是阻止它。
It worked! Course it did.
有效！当然做到了。
Now, just remember
the cardinal rule -
现在，只要记住
基本规则——
never step away from your stumps.
永远不要离开你的树桩。
Well, at least he's making himself
useful. Despite the injured air.
好吧，至少他让自己变得
有用了。尽管受伤的空气。
He feels you still owe him
an apology. Utter nonsense.
他觉得你还欠他
一个道歉。胡说八道。
PHONE RINGS
电话铃声
So, you played a lot of cricket
at school, then, did you, Triss?
所以，你
在学校打了很多板球，那么，你呢，特莉丝？
Yes, fair bit.
是的，公平一点。
Captain of the first 11,
weren't you? Darrowby, 2-2-9-7.
前11的队长，
不是吗？达罗比，2-2-9-7。
Yes, we had a pretty strong
team at the prep school.
是的，我们
在预科学校有一支非常强大的团队。
Even won the inter-school cup
three years in a row.
甚至连续
三年获得校际杯冠军。
I didn't know that.
我不知道。
No? We actually set a new
record for the Under 12s.
不？实际上，我们
为 12 岁以下儿童创造了新记录。
The old man came to every match.
老头子每场比赛都来。
Pa used to watch you play?
爸以前看你打球？
He'd drive up in the mornings
and we'd make a day of it.
他会在早上开车
，我们会度过一天。
You know how he loved cricket. Yes.
你知道他有多喜欢板球。是的。
Yes, I suppose he did.
是的，我想他做到了。
Mr Farnon, Mrs Pumphrey.
法农先生，普弗里太太。
She says she's in dire
need of your assistance.
她说她非常
需要你的帮助。
Mrs Pumphrey, what can I do for you?
Pumphrey 夫人，我能为您做什么？
The workmen were putting up the
tea tent for tomorrow, you see,
工人们正在
搭起明天的茶帐，你看，
and Francois was clearly distracted.
弗朗索瓦显然心烦意乱。
And, erm, poor Tricki, I mean,
he dashed through the main gate
而且，呃，可怜的特里奇，我是说，
他冲进了大门
and just ran and ran...
So Tricki is missing?
就跑
啊跑...所以特里奇失踪了？
Foot to the bridge of the ball,
James!
脚到球桥，
詹姆斯！
Well, no, not, not exactly.
He was, erm...
嗯，不，不，不完全是。
他是，呃...
He was heading in the
direction of Mr Handshaw's yard.
他正朝着
汉德肖先生的院子走去。
Ah. And I really can't ask
Francois... No, of course.
啊。我真的不能问
弗朗索瓦……不，当然。
Er, leave...leave it with me,
Mrs Pumphrey,
呃，离开……
交给我，Pumphrey 夫人，
you've nothing to worry about.
你没有什么可担心的。
Oh, thank you, thank you!
哦，谢谢，谢谢！
Mr Farnon, when you see Tricki,
法农先生，当你看到特里奇时，
could you pretend that you
just happened to be passing?
你能假装
刚好路过吗？
He's terribly private, I would
hate for him to be embarrassed.
他非常私密，我不想
让他感到尴尬。
I understand. Of course.
我明白。当然。
Aye, he's a determined
little bugger.
是的，他是一个坚定的
小家伙。
Well, as I say, Mrs Pumphrey
did want me to pass on
好吧，正如我所说，Pumphrey 夫人
确实希望我继续
her sincere apologies. Not to worry.
她真诚的道歉。不要担心。
It's not like he's some stray.
他不像是个流浪者。
A litter or two of pups wouldn't
be the end of the world.
一两窝幼崽不会
是世界末日。
Come on, then, young Trickiwoo,
来吧，年轻的特里奇乌，
let's put you back where you belong,
shall we?
让我们把你放回属于你的地方，
好吗？
See you at the match tomorrow,
Mr Handshaw.
汉德肖先生，明天比赛见。
Your brother still not playing? I'm
afraid not. That's a damned shame.
你哥还不玩？我
恐怕没有。那真是该死的耻辱。
Might've given us a fighting chance.
可能给了我们一个战斗的机会。
Well, now he's been there once,
嗯，现在他去过那里一次，
he'll be much more inclined
to visit again.
他会更愿意
再次访问。
Right, seems we have no choice.
对，看来我们别无选择。
It's a very simple procedure.
这是一个非常简单的程序。
In fact, I should be able to fit
him in on Monday. That soon?
事实上，
周一我应该能让他适应。这么快？
Well, all right.
If we must, we must.
好吧，好吧。
如果我们必须，我们必须。
But until then, you really need to
keep him on a lead.
但在那之前，你真的需要
让他保持领先。
Oh, Tricki.
哦，特里奇。
Will you ever forgive me?
你会原谅我吗？
All set for match tomorrow, I hope?
一切都准备好明天比赛，我希望？
Absolutely. Raring to go!
Oh, that's the spirit.
绝对地。迫不及待要去了！
哦，这就是精神。
And with James playing too, I really
think this might be your year.
有了詹姆斯也打球，我真的
认为这可能是你的一年。
I think we're all here.
我想我们都在这里。
Ladies and gentlemen, It's my very
great pleasure to welcome you all
女士们，先生们，我很
高兴欢迎大家
to Pumphrey Manor for this year's
encounter between The Darrowby 11
到 Pumphrey Manor 参加今年
与 The Darrowby 11的相遇
and the Hulton Hall Chaps.
和 Hulton Hall Chaps。
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
欢呼与掌声
Has anyone seen Mr Rudd?
有人见过陆先生吗？
We'll be playing a timed game, with
the last 20 overs from five o'clock.
我们将进行一场计时比赛，
从五点开始进行最后 20 场比赛。
And, erm, I know we're all looking
forward to seeing some
而且，嗯，我知道我们都期待
看到一些
excellent cricket.
优秀的板球。
TRICKI YAPS
特里奇·雅普斯
CROWD CHUCKLES
So, erm, wi...
人群咯咯笑
所以，呃，...
Without further ado, Mr Chapman?
Yeah?
不用多说，查普曼先生？
是的？
If you would do the honours.
如果你会做荣誉。
Certainly.
当然。
Well gentlemen, if you're ready,
will you two captains
先生们，如果你们准备好了，
你们两位船长好吗？
accompany me to the
crease with the coin toss, please?
陪我一起
抛硬币，好吗？
Thank you. Mr Alderson...
谢谢你。奥尔德森先生...
Mr Alderson. Young Rudds,
where's your father?
奥尔德森先生。年轻的路德斯，
你爸爸呢？
He can't come, Mr Alderson,
the sheep got out
他不能来，奥尔德森先生，
羊跑了
and he needs to round 'em up.
You're kidding me?
他需要四舍五入。
你在逗我吗？
No, we're not. We're not.
You're not.
没有，我们没有。不是。
你不。
So he's not coming?
所以他不来？
So we're a player short.
所以我们是一名球员。
Well, go on. You can't let them
go out wi' ten men.
好吧，继续。你不能让他们
带着十个人出去。
I can always play, Mr Alderson,
if that would be any help?
我总是可以玩，奥尔德森先生，
如果这有什么帮助吗？
Help? Yeah, that'd be a big help.
帮助？是的，那会有很大帮助。
Shame you didn't offer before.
可惜你之前没有提供。
Go and help your dad look for them
sheep.
去帮你爸爸找
羊。
Welcome to the team.
欢迎加入我们。
Yes, thanks.
THEY LAUGH
是啊谢谢。
他们笑了
Afternoon.
下午。
Mr Hulton, would you like to make
the call? Heads.
Hulton 先生，您要打个
电话吗？头。
We're bowling, lads.
我们在打保龄球，伙计们。
We're batting.
我们在击球。
Well, we've got to do it sometime.
I'd rather do it second, but...
好吧，我们必须在某个时候这样做。
我宁愿做第二件事，但是...
Herriot.
赫里奥特。
Hugh.
休。
Right, remember what
we did last year?
对了，还记得
我们去年做了什么吗？
Come on, boys, stay alert.
来吧，孩子们，保持警惕。
Go on, dad.
继续，爸爸。
Look lively, Herriot.
看起来很活泼，赫里奥特。
Come on, lads!
来吧，伙计们！
OK, play.
好，玩。
Knock to it, lads, come on!
Unlucky, unlucky!
敲门，小伙子们，来吧！
倒霉，倒霉！
Good shot...
好球...
Four!
四个！
Excellent opener, Mr Hulton.
优秀的开场白，赫尔顿先生。
Looks like Mr Hulton means business.
看起来 Hulton 先生是认真的。
Herriot.
赫里奥特。
Oh, good shot!
哦，拍得好！
Yours, Herriot!
你的，赫里奥特！
Get behind it.
落后于它。
Come on, James!
Unlucky.
加油，詹姆斯！
倒霉。
Just a single. Keepers' end.
只是一个。守门员的结局。
That's Hulton's 50.
那是赫尔顿的 50 岁。
Herriot.
赫里奥特。
James! Ball!
Come on, lad!
詹姆士！球！
来吧，小伙子！
Eye on the ball, Mr Herriot.
盯着球看，赫里奥特先生。
123...
..for no wickets.
..因为没有小门。
Not out.
不出来。
Chin up.
振奋起来。
Unlucky. Next time, lads.
倒霉。下次，伙计们。
James is looking a bit hot.
詹姆斯看起来有点热。
Hugh's giving him
a right runaround.
休给了他
一个正确的选择。
Helen.
海伦。
How are you?
Hello, Margot.
你好吗？
你好，玛戈。
Yeah, I'm fine thank you.
This is my sister, Jenny.
是的，我很好，谢谢。
这是我的妹妹，珍妮。
Hello.
你好。
Are you enjoying the match?
你享受比赛吗？
I will once we start getting
some wickets.
一旦我们开始获得
一些小门，我就会。
Oh, yes, of course.
哦，是的，当然。
Anyway, I'm sure I'll see
you in the tea tent.
不管怎样，我相信我会
在茶帐里见到你的。
What was all that about?
那是怎么回事？
Let's be having a wicket, Siegfried.
齐格弗里德，让我们有一个检票口。
Hello there.
Hello.
你好呀。
你好。
I noticed you were rather
tied to your post
我注意到你
对你的帖子很感兴趣
and thought you might
be in need of refreshment.
并认为您可能
需要提神。
Oh, that's very kind of you.
哦，你真是太好了。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Your Mr Farnon doesn't seem to be
having much luck.
你的法农先生似乎
不太走运。
Trouble is, he's overpitching.
问题是，他太调皮了。
When you say "overpitching"?
当你说“过分”？
He's landing the ball too
close to the batsman,
他的球
离击球手太近了，
making it easier to drive.
使其更容易驾驶。
Go on, James.
继续，詹姆斯。
He's making it harder for the
fielders.
他让
外野手更难了。
So he does.
所以他会。
Are you all right, there, Herriot?
你没事吧，赫里奥特？
Fine, thanks.
很好，谢谢。
Well,
you can't blame the bull this time.
好吧，
这次你不能责怪公牛。
HE FEIGNS LAUGHTER
他假装在笑
Would you mind changing that to 138?
你介意把它改成 138 吗？
Mr Chapman. Mm?
查普曼先生。毫米？
I think that's enough.
我认为这就够了。
Come on, Harry.
来吧，哈利。
Ah, and that's the declaration.
啊，这就是宣言。
Tea, everyone!
茶，大家！
What's happening?
发生了什么？
Hulton thinks he's got enough runs
to win so he's declared.
Hulton 认为他有足够的得分
来获胜，所以他宣布了。
He's stopping.
他要停下来了。
Well, that's good news for us,
isn't it? Aye.
嗯，这对我们来说
是个好消息，不是吗？是的。
If you like charity.
如果你喜欢慈善。
I could certainly use a cup of tea.
我当然可以用一杯茶。
Well, enjoy it while you can.
好吧，尽情享受吧。
We're batting next.
我们接下来要击球了。
And it won't be pretty.
而且不会很漂亮。
Pork pie, you love that.
猪肉馅饼，你喜欢那个。
Oh, yum-yum-yum. No?
哦，嗯，​​嗯，嗯。不？
Or how about a tiny piece of
iced bun?
或者一小
块冰面包怎么样？
LOW GROWL
低吼
Oh! Oh, Mr Farnon.
哦！哦，法农先生。
I hope you're not too disheartened.
我希望你不要太沮丧。
Oh, not at all.
哦，一点也不。
We've got a lot of strength
in our batting. That's the spirit.
我们
的击球能力很强。就是那种精神。
And, you have your secret weapon.
而且，你有你的秘密武器。
Your brother, of course.
当然是你的兄弟。
Yes.
是的。
He opened quite gloriously
last year.
他
去年开张得非常光彩。
He did do very well.
他做得很好。
Tricki, please.
特里奇，请。
He simply hates this horrid lead.
他只是讨厌这个可怕的领导。
Well, it's only till the operation.
嗯，这只是直到手术。
And what then?
然后呢？
Can you promise me
你能答应我吗
he'll still be my Tricki once he's
been emasculated?
一旦他
被阉割了，他还是我的特里奇吗？
Some dogs do present a slight
change in temperament.
有些狗的
性情确实会略有变化。
Yes, that's what I feared.
是的，这就是我害怕的。
It just feels too cruel.
只是觉得太残忍了。
Why shouldn't he be allowed to
express his true self
为什么不应该让他
表达真实的自己
and experience life to the full?
并充分体验生活？
And if Mr Handshaw were open to
an arrangement...
如果 Handshaw 先生愿意接受
安排......
Well,
he certainly gave that impression.
嗯，
他确实给人这种印象。
Well, what would you do, Mr Farnon?
好吧，你会怎么做，法农先生？
Do you know what, Mrs Pumphrey?
你知道吗，庞弗里夫人？
If I were you,
I would forget the lead
如果我是你，
我会忘记主角
and just let Tricki do what
comes naturally.
就让特里奇做
自然而然的事情。
Life's just too short, isn't it?
生命太短暂了，不是吗？
I knew you would understand.
我知道你会明白的。
Hugh, could I speak to you for a
moment?
休，我能跟你说
一会儿吗？
Course.
课程。
I just want to say, how,
how sorry I am.
我只想说，
我多么，多么抱歉。
For everything that happened.
对于发生的一切。
That's water under the bridge.
那是桥下的水。
No, I know, but I've not had chance
to apologise properly.
不，我知道，但我没有机会
好好道歉。
In person.
亲自。
I never wanted to hurt you.
我从来不想伤害你。
We just weren't right for one
another.
我们只是不适合
彼此。
And I knew I wouldn't make
you happy.
我知道我不会让
你开心。
Well, I admit I...I was rather
devastated.
好吧，我承认我......我相当
沮丧。
But in a way,
once the worst has happened,
但在某种程度上，
一旦最糟糕的事情发生了，
it's actually rather freeing.
它实际上是相当自由的。
And I think part of me
always knew it wasn't right.
而且我认为我的一部分
总是知道这是不对的。
That we were good pals
and I know you were fond of me,
我们是好朋友
，我知道你喜欢我，
but...well, it was never a grand
passion, really, was it?
但是……嗯，这从来都不是一种盛大的
激情，真的，是吗？
Well, no.
嗯，不。
Maybe not.
也许不吧。
Maybe one day we can be pals again.
也许有一天我们可以再次成为好朋友。
I'd like that.
我愿意。
About the bull.
关于公牛。
It was such a generous
thing to do... Did I overstep?
这是
一件多么慷慨的事情……我是不是越界了？
Because that,
that really wasn't my intention.
因为那
真的不是我的本意。
And me Dad knows you meant well.
We both do.
我爸爸知道你的意思很好。
我们都这样做。
But we can't accept it.
但我们不能接受。
Right.
对。
Pay our own way.
支付我们自己的方式。
Always have.
一直有。
And you've no reason to feel you
have to make amends.
而且你没有理由觉得你
必须做出补偿。
Didn't realise Herriot was
a cricketer.
没有意识到赫里奥特是
一名板球运动员。
Oh,
he stepped in at the last minute.
哦，
他在最后一刻介入了。
Ah, keen to impress the Captain,
no doubt.
啊，
毫无疑问，渴望给船长留下深刻印象。
We only started seeing each other
quite recently.
我们
最近才开始见面。
I mean,
there were nothing going on before.
我的意思是，
之前什么都没有发生。
Helen, really,
I'm just glad you're happy.
海伦，真的，
我很高兴你开心。
Well, I'd better get
back to the others.
好吧，我最好
回到其他人那里。
Discuss strategy and all that.
讨论战略等等。
Hello. Oh, there you are...
你好。哦，你在这儿...
I saw you chatting with Hugh.
我看到你在和休聊天。
Yeah. We had a really good talk.
是的。我们谈得真好。
I feel like we cleared the air.
我觉得我们净化了空气。
Right.
对。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I just wondered why
he was kissing you.
我只是想知道
他为什么要吻你。
Kissing me?
亲我？
Oh, that were nothing.
Right.
哦，那没什么。
对。
He just wants to be friends.
他只想做朋友。
And he's given you a pedigree
bull to prove it.
他给了你一头纯种
公牛来证明这一点。
Yeah, well, I've said I'm not
accepting the bull.
是的，好吧，我说过我不
接受公牛。
You're not?
你不？
Course not.
当然不是。
It were a kind gesture,
but we're not in need of charity,
这是一种善意的姿态，
但我们不需要施舍，
however well meant.
不过好意。
Now, then Herriot.
现在，然后是赫里奥特。
I'll put you up to bat last with
you being a novice.
作为新手，我会让你坚持到最后。
Right.
Very good.
对。
非常好。
Yeah. Let's hope that Hugh takes it
easy with you.
是的。让我们希望 Hugh 能
轻松对待你。
Right, ladies and gentlemen, I think
we are ready to resume.
是的，女士们，先生们，我想
我们已经准备好重新开始了。
Hulton's looking deadly serious.
赫尔顿看起来非常严肃。
But then I suppose he's
a lot riding on this.
但后来我想他
很在意这个。
How d'you mean? Well, all those
months he spent in France,
你是什​​么意思？好吧，
他在法国度过的那几个月，
too embarrassed to show his face.
太不好意思露脸了。
He'll be wanting a win to
restore his dignity. Triss!
他会想要一场胜利来
恢复他的尊严。特莉丝！
Lovely shot, Tristan.
漂亮的镜头，特里斯坦。
Cracking shot, Tristan!
开枪，特里斯坦！
Go on, Triss.
继续，特莉丝。
Brilliant!
杰出的！
Again.
再次。
CHEERING
欢呼
GROANING
呻吟
Nicely done. Good running, lads.
做得很好。跑得好，伙计们。
Stay.
停留。
GROANING
呻吟
That's unlucky.
那是倒霉。
Now that's called a batting
collapse.
现在这被称为击球
崩溃。
It's more exciting than I'd
anticipated.
这比我
预期的更令人兴奋。
We'll make a cricket convert
of you yet.
我们会让你成为蟋蟀的转换
者。
You know, I walk Rock
down by Copley Brook most evenings.
你知道，
大多数晚上我都会在科普利溪边散步。
If you're ever out with Jess
and want a bit of company.
如果你曾经和 Jess 一起出去，
想要一点陪伴。
Well...perhaps we'll see you down
there.
好吧……也许我们会在
那里见到你。
Last over. Doubt you'll be needed.
最后结束。怀疑你会被需要。
They need to get two
wickets before you go in
在你进去之前，他们需要得到两个检票口
and Siegfried is looking strong.
齐格弗里德看起来很强壮。
Catch it. Yes!
抓住它。是的！
Just four balls to face, Henry.
只需要面对四个球，亨利。
Good luck, Henry.
Come on, Henry. Thanks, lads.
祝你好运，亨利。
来吧，亨利。谢谢，伙计们。
All the best, Henry.
一切顺利，亨利。
Play.
玩。
GASPS
气体安全保护系统
I spoke too soon.
我说得太快了。
Right, Herriot, get padded up.
对了，赫里奥特，收拾收拾。
Henry's retiring hurt.
亨利的退休受伤了。
There's three balls left till
the end of the game.
到
比赛结束还剩三个球。
If they don't get you out,
we'll draw.
如果他们不让你出去，
我们就抽签。
And that's as good as a win.
Just do what you can.
这和胜利一样好。
做你能做的。
All you have to do is stay in,
old chap.
你所要做的就是呆在里面，
老家伙。
Remember what we practised.
记住我们练习的内容。
Protect your wicket
and guard your stumps.
保护您的检票口
并保护您的树桩。
Middle leg.
中腿。
That'll do.
这样就行了。
Go on, lad.
加油，小伙子。
Three balls to come.
三个球来了。
GROANING AND MURMURING
呻吟和抱怨
Fine.
美好的。
You all right, Jim?
你还好吗，吉姆？
Well done, James.
干得好，詹姆斯。
Run.
跑。
It's gone for four.
四点没了。
Back this end, old chap.
回到这一点，老家伙。
Last ball of the match.
比赛的最后一球。
Just block it again,
exactly the same as before,
再屏蔽一次，
和之前一模一样，
and Hugh'll be
crying into his beer tonight.
今晚休会在他的啤酒里哭。
Come on, Mr Herriot. Come on, James.
来吧，赫里奥特先生。来吧，詹姆斯。
Unlucky, batsman.
不幸的是，击球手。
Hard luck, lad.
运气不好，小伙子。
Thanks, Bert.
谢谢，伯特。
Funny that, almost looked like you
deliberately stepped
有趣的是，几乎看起来像你
故意踩
away from the wicket.
远离检票口。
Why ever would I do that?
我为什么要那样做？
I've absolutely no idea.
我完全不知道。
Hey. Bad luck, Mr Herriot.
嘿。运气不好，赫里奥特先生。
Nearly had a draw there.
那里差点有平局。
Aye, still, well played, lads.
是的，仍然，打得很好，小伙子们。
They were a tough side
and no mistake.
他们是强硬的一方
，没有错。
You carried your bat.
你带着你的蝙蝠。
Great achievement.
伟大的成就。
Both of you.
你们俩。
The old man would be proud.
老人会很自豪的。
That's, erm, very fine batting,
young Farnon.
那是，嗯，非常好的击球，
年轻的法农。
James didn't do too badly either.
詹姆斯的表现也不算差。
Till he lost his nerve.
直到他失去了理智。
Dad!
爸爸！
Oh, well, I'm only saying it to him.
哦，好吧，我只是对他说。
Good try, Uncle Herriot.
很好的尝试，赫里奥特叔叔。
Thank you, Mrs Pumphrey.
谢谢你，庞弗里夫人。
Well done, Triss.
Thanks, Helen.
干得好，特莉丝。
谢谢，海伦。
Well done.
做得好。
I don't think your dad's too happy.
我觉得你爸爸不太高兴。
Don't worry about him.
不用担心他。
James, I just wanted to say...
詹姆斯，我只想说……
..well played.
..打的好。
You too.
你也是。
I suppose the best team won.
我想最好的球队赢了。
Still, that took real grit.
尽管如此，这还是需要勇气的。
Anyway, have a good evening.
不管怎样，晚上好。
Both of you.
你们俩。
So how does it feel?
那么感觉如何呢？
What? To have missed the most
important ball of the match?
什么？错过
了比赛中最重要的球？
Is that what you did?
那是你做的吗？
I felt I owed him a win.
我觉得我欠他一场胜利。
I know.
我知道。
And I love you for it.
我爱你。
You do?
你做？
Yes, I suppose I do.
是的，我想我知道。
Thank you, George.
谢谢你，乔治。
Ah.
啊。
To your very good health.
祝您身体健康。
Cheers.
干杯。
You know, I don't remember Pa ever
visiting me at school.
你知道，我不记得爸爸曾经
在学校拜访过我。
No? He used to take me
out on his rounds, though.
不？不过，他过去常常带我
出去巡视。
I was nine
when I delivered my first lamb.
当我生下第一只羊羔时，我九岁。
And you've never looked back.
而你从未回头。
No, I suppose I didn't.
不，我想我没有。
I owe you an apology, Tristan.
我欠你一个道歉，特里斯坦。
For not telling you
the truth about your results.
因为没有告诉你
关于你的结果的真相。
I genuinely believed
I was acting in your best interests.
我真的相信
我是在为你的最佳利益行事。
Right.
对。
But I realise now, that
I may have been...wrong.
但我现在意识到，
我可能已经……错了。
Anyway, the money's there,
反正钱到了
if you decide you want to go
back to college.
如果你决定要
回大学。
Equally,
if you feel it's not for you,
同样，
如果你觉得它不适合你，
well, it should be your decision.
好吧，这应该是你的决定。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Here he is! "An hour to play
and the last man in."
他在这里！“还有一个小时的比赛
，最后一个人进来。”
I think he did very well.
我认为他做得很好。
How're the ribs?
肋骨怎么样？
Bit sore, to be honest.
说实话，有点痛。
Oh, you poor old thing.
哦，你这个可怜的老东西。
No Tricki Woo, Mrs Pumphrey?
没有特里奇胡，Pumphrey 夫人？
Tricki.
技巧。
Yes, Tricki has some personal
business to attend to.
是的，Tricki 有一些私人
事务要处理。
Think it's time I made my move.
认为是时候采取行动了。
Well played, darling.
打得好，亲爱的。
Hugh and Margot?
休和玛格特？
Wait, are they...?
等等，他们是……？
I think you've missed your chance,
Triss.
我想你已经错过了机会，
特莉丝。
Bad luck, old chap.
运气不好，老伙计。
Well,
she wasn't really my type anyway.
好吧，
无论如何她都不是我喜欢的类型。
Since when?
从何时起？
No, it's true, she was...a bit too
tall.
不，是真的，她……有点太高了
。
Oh, for heaven's sake.
哦，看在上帝的份上。
She's a woman, not a pony.
她是女人，不是小马。
Oh, height is a consideration.
哦，高度是一个考虑因素。
You should be so lucky.
Nothing wrong with tall.
你应该很幸运。
身材高大没什么不好。
I'm a catch.
我是个陷阱。
You're a liability.
你是一种责任。
THEY LAUGH
他们笑了
SNORTING
打鼾
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
Red Bee Media 字幕